{
    "contents": {
        "title":"Category",
        "name":"Sports",
        "questionsList": [{
                "question1":{
                    "question": "Which is our national Sport?",
                    "answer": ["H","O","C","K","E","Y"],
                    "duration": 30
                },
                "question2":{
                    "question": "Who won the first T20 World Cup?",
                    "answer": ["I","N","D","I","A"],
                    "duration": 30
                },
                "question3":{
                    "question": "Which country has won the Cricket World Cup three times in a row?",
                    "answer": ["A","U","S","T","R","A","L","I","A"],
                    "duration": 30
                },
                "question4":{
                    "question": "How many times has India won the ICC World Cup?",
                    "answer": ["T","W","O"],
                    "duration": 30
                },
                "question5":{
                    "question": "Who is known as the Flying Sikh of India?",
                    "answer": ["M","I","L","K","A","S","I","N","G","H"],
                    "duration": 30
                },
                "question6":{
                    "question": "How many times has India won the Hockey World Cup (Menâ€™s)?",
                    "answer": ["O","N","E"],
                    "duration": 30
                },
                "question7":{
                    "question": "Name the woman boxer who won the medal in world championships",
                    "answer": ["M","A","R","Y","K","O","M"],
                    "duration": 30
                },
                "question8":{
                    "question": "Name the woman who is the first Indian to win a medal in Badminton at the Olympics",
                    "answer": ["S","A","I","N","A","N","E","H","W","A","L"],
                    "duration": 30
                },
                "question9":{
                    "question": "who is known as the God of Cricket",
                    "answer": ["S","A","C","H","I","N"],
                    "duration": 30
                },
                "question10":{
                    "question": "In which country commonwealth games were held in 2010?",
                    "answer": ["I","N","D","I","A"],
                    "duration": 30
                }
            }
        ]
    }
}